{
    "parts": [
        {
            "question": "Which is the smallest planet within our solar system?", 
            "answer": "Mercury"
        },
        {
            "question": "The moon called Titan orbits which planet?", 
            "answer": "Saturn"
        }, 
        {
            "question": "Which planet is larger, Neptune or Saturn?", 
            "answer": "Saturn"
        }, 
        {
            "question": "There have been more missions to this planet versus any other planet", 
            "answer": "Mars"
        }, 
        {
            "question": "What protects Earth from meteoroids and radiation from the sun?", 
            "answer": "It's Atmosphere"
        }, 
        {
            "question": "How many of our planets can be seen without a telescope?", 
            "answer": "5"
        }, 
        {
            "question": "Which planet is closest in size to Earth?", 
            "answer": "Venus"
        }, 
        { 
            "question": "Which planet has the most moons?", 
            "answer": "Saturn"
        }, 
        {
            "question": "Which planets have no moons?", 
            "answer": "Mercury and Venus"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the oldest planet in our solar system?", 
            "answer": "Jupiter"
        }
    ]
}